orangesubmit.com 2011-05-28

# OrangeSoda | View the OrangeSoda Privacy Policy Here

At OrangeSoda, we respect and protect the privacy of our clients and users who visit our websites. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect and use information for OrangeSoda services, including the advertising services, promotions, informational mailings and other offers we provide. By using any services provided by OrangeSoda, Inc. (“OrangeSoda”), you indicate that you agree to the collection and use of your information by OrangeSoda as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

## Why We Collect Information

First and foremost, OrangeSoda collects information to improve the services we provide and to present you with information and services that will interest you. We also use your information to measure our success and performance. For example, aggregate information gives us an idea of the number of visitors we attract and how they navigate our websites.

## Personal Information Collection

OrangeSoda is the sole owner of information collected on this website. Any personal information that is collected by us is provided by you strictly on a voluntary basis. You may submit your personal information in a number of ways, depending on the Orange Soda service you are using and your choices while using our services. For example, if you choose to run an advertising campaign through OrangeSoda, during registration we may ask you for, and you may choose to give to us, information such as your name, e-mail address, physical address, telephone number, credit card information or other personal information necessary to complete a transaction or provide services to you. We use this information, such as your email address, to send users information about our company, client campaigns and its products and services if requested or if necessary. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. We provide you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes by [emailingunsubscribe@orangesoda.com](mailto:emailingunsubscribe@orangesoda.com) at any time.

You may submit your credit card information online or over the phone when you sign up for our services. We process payments through Propay, Inc., GlobalPayments, and AuthorizeNET. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any purpose other than billing for our services.

We will not share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this privacy policy.

## Use of Personal Information

As stated above, unless you voluntarily provide personal information for a specific purpose, we do not collect personal information from you. We will never combine any personal information about a user of our site with any aggregate information we collect about that user, whether collected on our site or our Advertising Service. If you choose to provide personal information during registration or when using our services, we use your personal information to provide you with particular product or services that you request. If your personal information changes, you may correct, update or delete it by emailing our Customer Support at [cs@orangesoda.com](mailto:cs@orangesoda.com) or by calling 1-800-637-9140.

OrangeSoda will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. However, we may transfer personal information in connection with a sale or merger of OrangeSoda or the division responsible for the services provided to you. We may also share your personal information, such as your email address, mailing address, etc., with our technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who make our site available, enhance its functionality or provide associated services and/or who deal with you in processing your orders and/or delivering content, samples, products, services and gifts and prizes. These third parties are not allowed to use personal information except for the purposes of providing the applicable services. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. Our site and services are maintained in the United States of America . By using the site and/or services, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

#### Other Information We Collect and Use

We may collect non-personally identifiable information with cookies, such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. This aggregate information is analyzed and combined with similar aggregate information of other users and may be collected both on our site and on other sites in our Advertising Service. We may share aggregate information with our business partners and other third parties. Such aggregate information is anonymous and does not identify any individual user, and we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use proprietary Otracking.com persistent cookies and adhere to a strict P3P tracking policy (for more information, visit <http://otracking.com/w3c/policy.html>). You can remove persistent cookies by following directions on your Internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, and administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Third Party Website Links

Some of our websites provide links to third-party websites, such as those of our affiliates, business partners and advertisers. We have no access to or control over their practices. Because OrangeSoda does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties websites, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personal information.

## Security Information

OrangeSoda stores all data using industry standard security devices, such as firewalls and encryption protocols, to prevent against unauthorized access to our data. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures coupled with carefully developed security procedures to protect your information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration. When we ask for sensitive information, such as credit card numbers, we protect it through the use of the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol which provides encryption during transmission.

We have put in place policies to restrict access to your information by our employees. Our employees are trained to safeguard your information. Additionally, we use internal and external resources to review the adequacy of our security procedures.

#### Protection for Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13.

#### TRUSTe Privacy Program

OrangeSoda is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the website [http://www.orangesoda.com](http://www.orangesoda.com/). Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Tamara at [privacypolicy@orangesoda.com](mailto:privacypolicy@orangesoda.com) . If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contract TRUSTe athttp://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liason with us to resolve your concerns.

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes to this privacy statement onwww.orangesoda.com and other places we deem appropriate so you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. Your continued use of the site after such changes have been posted indicates your consent and acceptance of such changes.

## Effective Date

This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated on April 6, 2007
